A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  - Medicine, 1982-1986; 17; 26.2 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes and 2 half-letter boxes
    - Hospitals, 3
      - Massachusetts General Hospital (Box 471, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - A-C (Box 471, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - C-N (Box 472, Folder 1-3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - O-Z (Box 473, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Annual Report, 1981-1986 (Box 473, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Managers-Board of Overseers (Box 474, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Managers-Board of Overseers - LSR Retirement (Box 474, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Centennial (Box 474, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Christmas Party (Box 474, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Clippings (Box 474, Folder 5, Box 475, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions, 1977-1981 (Box 475, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions, 1982-1986 (Box 475, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 475, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1977-1983 (Box 476, Folder 1-4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions - Rockefeller family Gifts, 1974-1985 (Box 477, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Documents living Rockefeller family members.
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions - Rockefeller family - JY Ranch (Box 477, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller Trust, 1970-1983 (Box 477, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Convocation (Box 478, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Employees (Box 478, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Endowed Chairs (Box 478, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances (Box 479, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Open in 2029
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Audits (Box 479, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Investments (Box 479, Folder 3-4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Audit Committee (Box 480, Folder 1-3, Box 481, Box 482, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Finance and Funding Committee (Box 482, Folder 3, Box 483, Folder 1-3, Box 484, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Finance and Funding Committee - Budget Subcommittee (Box 484, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Finance and Funding Committee - Investment Subcommitttee (Box 484, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company (Box 484, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - General (Box 478, Folder 4, Box 485, Folder 1-2, Box 486)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - A-D (Box 486, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - E-Z (Box 487, Folder 1-3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Annual Appeal (Box 487, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Vincent Astor Foundation (Box 488, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - J.M Foundation (Box 488, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Haupt, Mrs. Enid A. (Box 488, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Hess, Leon (Box 488, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Klug, John W. (Box 488, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Petrie, Milton (Box 488, Folder 6)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sherwan Fairchild Foundation (Box 489, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Corporate Development - General (Box 488, Folder 7)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Corporate Development - A-Z (Box 489, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Japan (Box 489, Folder 3-4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Memorial Sloan Kettering of Canada (Box 490, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra VI - General (Box 490, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra VI - A-Z (Box 490, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra VI - Financial Reports (Box 490, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra IV - Co-Chairmen (Box 490, Folder 6)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra V - General (Box 491, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra V - A-Z (Box 491, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra V - Co-Chairmen (Box 491, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra V - Financial Reports (Box 491, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra IV (Box 491, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra IV - Co-Chairmen - A-Z (Box 492, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra V - Financial Reports (Box 492, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra-Pavarotti (Box 492, Folder 3-5)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra-Pavarotti - A-Z (Box 493, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra-Pavarotti - Co-Chairmen (Box 493, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra-Pavarotti - Associate Chairmen (Box 493, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Information Systems Strategic Plan (Box 493, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Interferon Program (Box 494, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Joint Nominating Committee (Box 494, Folder 2-4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Long Range Planning (Box 494, Folder 5, Box 495, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Long Range Planning Subcommittee of the Institutional Policy Committee (Box 495, Folder 3, Box 496, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Annual Meetings (Box 496, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Managers (Box 496, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Overseers-Board of Managers (Box 496, Folder 4, Box 497, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 497, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Institutional Policy Committee (Box 497, Folder 3-5, Box 498, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Minutes-Meetings - Joint Organizational Policy Committee (Box 498, Folder 3-4, Box 499, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Nuclear Magnetic Resource Unit (NMR) (Box 499, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Organization (Box 499, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - President's Council (Box 499, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Printed Matter (Box 500, Folder 1-2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Printed Matter - Center News (Box 500, Folder 3-5)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories (Box 501, Folder 1-3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller Research Laboratories - Ground Breaking (Box 502, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - John D. Rockefeller Jr. Research Center - LSR Gift (Box 502, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Agendas (Box 502, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Donors (Box 502, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Staff - A-Z (Box 503, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Personnel
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Staff - Thomas, Lewis (Box 503, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Staff - Marks, Paul A., 1980-1986 (Box 503, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Taxes (Box 503, Folder 4)
        Restricted - Confidential financial material
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Works of Art (Box 504, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases (Box 504, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - A-Z (Box 504, Folder 3)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (Box 504, Folder 4)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Contributions (Box 505, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Minuites-Meetings (Box 505, Folder 2)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Mount Desert Island Hospital (Box 505, Folder 3)
      - New York Medical College (Box 505, Folder 4-5)
      - Northern Westchester Hospitals and Association, Mt. Kisco, NY (Box 506, Folder 1)
      - Phelps Memorial Hospital Center, North Tarrytown, NY (Box 506, Folder 2)
      - St, Barnabas Hospital, New York (Box 506, Folder 3-5, Box 507, Folder 1)
      - St. Luke's Roosevelt Hospital Center (Box 507, Folder 2)
      - St. Vincent's Hospital and Medical Center of New York (Box 507, Folder 3)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center (Box 508, Folder 1)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Annual Reports (Box 507, Folder 4)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Board of Governors - Board of Managers (Box 508, Folder 2)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Contributions (Box 508, Folder 3)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - 50th Anniversary (Box 508, Folder 4)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Distinguished Professorship in Endocrinology (Box 508, Folder 5)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Meetings - Cornell University Medical College (Box 509, Folder 1-2)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Printed Matter (Box 509, Folder 3-4)
      - Society of New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Westchester Division (Box 510, Folder 1)
      - United Hospital Fund of New York (Box 510, Folder 2)
    - Mental Health, 4
      - Mental Health - A-H (Box 510, Folder 3)
      - Mental Health - I-Z (Box 511, Folder 1)
      - American Family Foundation (Box 511, Folder 2-4)
      - Blueberry Treatment Centers, Inc. (Box 512, Folder 1)
      - Hospital Audiences (Box 512, Folder 2)
      - C.G. Jung Institute of San Francisco (Box 512, Folder 3)
      - Massachusetts Association for Mental Health Inc. (Box 512, Folder 4)
      - Mental Health Law Project (Box 512, Folder 5)
      - National Alliance for the Mentally Ill (Box 513, Folder 1)
      - North Charles Mental Health Research and Training Foundation (Box 513, Folder 2-4)
      - Predictive Profiles International (Box 514, Folder 1)
    - Narcotics, 5
      - Narcotics - A-Z (Box 514, Folder 2)
      - American Council on Marijuana and other Pschoative Drugs (Box 514, Folder 3)
      - Phoenix House and Foundation (Box 514, Folder 4-5)
  - N-P, 1982-1986; 18; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - N - Miscellaneous (Box 515, Folder 1)
    - National News Council (Box 515, Folder 2-3)
    - O - Miscellaneous (Box 515, Folder 4)
    - P - Miscellaneous (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Philanthropy, 1982-1986; 19; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - Philanthropy - A-G (Box 515, Folder 6)
    - Philanthropy - H-Z (Box 516, Folder 1)
    - Battelle Memorial Institute (Box 516, Folder 2)
    - Council on Foundations (Box 516, Folder 3)
    - Independent Sector (Box 516, Folder 4, Box 517, Folder 1)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy (Box 517, Folder 2-3)
    - New York Community Trust (Box 517, Folder 4)
    - John D. Rockefeller Awards in Philanthropy (Box 517, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd Book (Box 518, Folder 1)
  - Politics, 1982-1986; 8.73 Cubic Feet 23 letter document boxes
    - Politics - A-E (Box 518, Folder 2-4)
    - Politics - F-N (Box 519, Folder 1-4)
    - Politics - N-Z (Box 520, Folder 1-4)
    - Capitol Hill Club (Box 521, Folder 1)
    - Citizens for America (Box 521, Folder 2)
    - Committee for the Study of the American Electorate (Box 521, Folder 3, Box 522, Folder 1)
    - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy (Box 522, Folder 2-3)
    - Common Cause (Box 524, Folder 1)
    - Dayton, Mark (Box 523, Folder 1)
    - Dayton, Mark - Public Relations - Articles (Box 523, Folder 2-3)
    - Democracy Project (Box 524, Folder 2-3)
    - Freeze Voter (Box 524, Folder 4)
    - Freeze Voter '84 (Box 525, Folder 1)
    - Fund for Constitutional Government (Box 525, Folder 2-4, Box 526, Folder 1-2)
    - The Future Fund (Box 526, Folder 3-4)
    - Human Serve Fund (Box 526, Folder 5, Box 527, Folder 1)
    - Institute for Public Policy Advocacy (Box 527, Folder 2)
    - Interface (Box 527, Folder 3-4)
    - Maine Nuclear Referendum Committee (Box 528, Folder 1)
    - Montana Coalition Fund (Box 528, Folder 2)
    - National Student Campaign for Voter Registration (Box 528, Folder 3)
    - National Women's Political Caucus (Box 529, Folder 1)
    - New Populist Forum (Box 528, Folder 4)
    - New York Republican County Committee (Box 529, Folder 2)
    - New York Republican State Committee (Box 529, Folder 3)
    - New York State Senate Republican Campaign Committee (Box 529, Folder 4)
    - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign (Box 529, Folder 5, Box 530, Folder 1-4)
    - Percy, Charles H. (Box 531, Folder 1)
    - Project Vote (Box 531, Folder 2-3)
    - Public Agenda Foundation (Box 531, Folder 4, Box 532, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Citizen, Inc., 1982-1987 (Box 533, Folder 1-4)
    - Republican National Congressional Committee (Box 534, Folder 1)
    - Republican National Finance Committee (Republican National Committee) (Box 534, Folder 2-3)
    - Republican National Senatorial Committee (Box 534, Folder 4-5)
    - Republican Senate House Dinner (Box 535, Folder 1)
    - Ripon Society (Box 535, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV (Box 535, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV - Contributions (Box 535, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV - Clippings (Box 535, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV - Fundraising (Box 535, Folder 6, Box 536, Folder 1)
    - Political Organization - Westchester Republican County Committee (Box 536, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - A-C (Box 536, Folder 3-5)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - D-G (Box 537, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - H-L (Box 538, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - M-Q (Box 539, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions - R-Z (Box 540, Folder 1-3)
  - Population, 1982-1986; 21; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
    - Population - A-Z (Box 541, Folder 1-2)
    - Association for Voluntary Sterilization (Box 541, Folder 3, Box 542, Folder 1)
    - Association for Voluntary Sterilization - Contributions (Box 542, Folder 2)
    - Center for Population Options (Box 542, Folder 3)
    - Center for Population Options - Printed Matter (Box 542, Folder 4)
    - Centre for Development and Population Activities (Box 542, Folder 5)
    - Global Tomorrow Coalition, Inc. (Box 543, Folder 1)
    - The Alan Guttmacher Institute (Box 543, Folder 2)
    - The Alan Guttmacher Institute - Contributions (Box 543, Folder 3)
    - Maternity Center Association (Box 543, Folder 4)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation-Western Hemispher Region, Inc. (Box 544, Folder 1)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 544, Folder 2)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Contributions (Box 544, Folder 3)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Printed Material (Box 544, Folder 4)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. (Box 545, Folder 1)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Contributions (Box 545, Folder 2)
    - Population Council (Box 545, Folder 3)
    - Population Council - Contributions (Box 545, Folder 4)
    - Population Council - Finances (Box 545, Folder 5)
    - Population Council - Fundraising (Box 545, Folder 6)
    - Population Council - Minutes-Meetings (Box 546, Folder 1)
    - Population Council - Printed Material (Box 546, Folder 2)
    - Population Crisis Committee (Box 546, Folder 3)
    - Population Crisis Committee - Contributions (Box 546, Folder 4)
    - Population Education, Inc. (Box 547, Folder 1)
    - Population Institute (Box 547, Folder 2)
    - Abortion - A-Z (Box 547, Folder 3)
    - Abortion - Catholics for a Free Choice (Box 548, Folder 1)
    - Abortion - Citizens Against Referendum 1 (Box 548, Folder 2)
    - Abortion - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) (Box 548, Folder 3, Box 549, Folder 1)
  - Q-R, 1982-1986; 22; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - R - Miscellaneous (Box 549, Folder 2)
    - Race Relations - A-M (Box 549, Folder 3-5)
    - Race Relations - N-Z (Box 550, Folder 1-2)
  - Race Relations, 1982-1986; 23; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - Catholic Interracial Council (Box 550, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Southern Studies (Box 550, Folder 4)
    - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law (Box 550, Folder 5)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Box 551, Folder 1)
    - NAACP - Contributions - Special Contribution Fund (Box 551, Folder 2)
    - NAACP - Contributions - Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc. (Box 551, Folder 3)
    - National Urban League (Box 551, Folder 4, Box 552, Folder 1-2)
    - National Urban League - Printed Matter (Box 552, Folder 3)
    - New York Urban Coalition (Box 552, Folder 4)
    - New York Urban League (Box 552, Folder 5)
    - Southern Regional Council (Box 552, Folder 6, Box 553, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate, 1982-1986; 24; 20.49 Cubic Feet 49 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes
    - Real Estate - A-Z, 1
      - Real Estate - A-H (Box 553, Folder 2-4)
      - Real Estate - I-Z (Box 554, Folder 1-3)
      - Dallas International Center (Box 554, Folder 4)
      - Interstate North Associates (Box 581, Folder 1)
      - Long Island Resort (Box 581, Folder 2)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - A-Z (Box 581, Folder 3-5)
      - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Smart, Richard P. (Box 581, Folder 6)
      - Mauna Lani Resort, Inc. (Box 582, Folder 1)
      - Frederick Melhado (Box 582, Folder 2)
      - Murphree Company (Box 582, Folder 3)
      - Olohana Corporation - A-L (Box 582, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller Garage (Box 582, Folder 5)
      - Seal Harbor (Box 603, Folder 4)
      - Seal Harbor - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden (Box 603, Folder 5)
      - Seal Harbor - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - Johnson, Peter J. (Box 604, Folder 2-3, Box 605, Folder 1)
      - Valley Ranch, Cody, WY (Box 605, Folder 2)
    - Embarcadero Center, 2
      - Embarcadero Center (Box 554, Folder 5, Box 555, Folder 1-4, Box 556, Folder 1)
      - Embarcadero Center - A-Z (Box 556, Folder 2)
      - Finances, 1983-1986 (Box 556, Folder 3-4)
      - Minutes-Meetings, 1983-1986 (Box 557, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed Matter (Box 557, Folder 3)
    - Enterprise Foundation, Inc., 3
      - Enterprise Foundation, Inc. (Box 558, Folder 1)
      - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 558, Folder 2)
      - David Rockefeller (Box 558, Folder 3)
    - Estate Fountain River, 4
      - Estate Fountain River - A-Z (Box 559, Folder 1-2)
      - Finances (Box 559, Folder 3-4)
      - Sale (Box 559, Folder 5)
      - Sale - A-Z (Box 560, Folder 1-2)
      - Sale - Delray Land, Inc. (Box 560, Folder 3-4, Box 561, Folder 1-2)
      - Sale - Delray Land, Inc. - Financing Arrangements (Box 562, Folder 1)
      - Sale - St. Croix Project (Box 562, Folder 2, Box 563, Folder 1)
      - St. Croix - George Hortzog Study from C.W. Frye, Jr., 1984 October (Box 563, Folder 2)
      - Jacobus' Hotel at Davis Bay, 1984 October (Box 563, Folder 3)
      - Jacobus, Geo H. - Option Agreement, 1983 June 22; October 1984 (Box 563, Folder 4)
      - Jacobus, Geo H. - Zoning, 1984 October (Box 563, Folder 5)
      - Landauer Appraisal, 1984 October (Box 563, Folder 6)
      - St. Croix - Lawetz - Farm Lease Agreement, 1984 October (Box 564, Folder 1-2)
      - St. Croix - New England Land - Jessie F. Sammis, 1984 October (Box 564, Folder 3)
      - Sotheby Parke-Bernet - Agreement, 1984 October (Box 564, Folder 4)
      - St. Croix - Option Agreement Estate Fountain River and Delray Land, 1984 October (Box 564, Folder 5-6)
      - St, Croix - Jacobus, Geo H. Correspondence, 1984 October (Box 564, Folder 7, Box 565, Folder 1)
      - Sale - Peters, Jacques J. (Box 565, Folder 2-3)
      - Sale - Wells, Patrick (Box 566, Folder 1-3)
    - Greenrock Corporation, 5
      - Pocantico Hills - A-Z (Box 567, Folder 1-2)
        Restricted - Open in 2042
      - Pocantico Hills - Accounting Manual (Box 567, Folder 3)
      - Pocantico Hills - Board of Directors (Box 568, Folder 1)
      - Pocantico Hills - Employees (Box 568, Folder 2-3)
        Restricted - Personnel records
      - Pocantico Hills - Finances, 1982-1986 (Box 568, Folder 4, Box 569, Folder 1-2)
      - Pocantico Hills - Meetings (Box 569, Folder 3)
      - Pocantico Hills - Memos (Box 569, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills, 6
      - Pocantico Hills (Box 570, Folder 1)
      - Pocantico Hills - Appraisals (Box 570, Folder 2-3, Box 571, Folder 1-2, Box 572, Folder 1-3)
      - Pocantico Hills - Hackley School (Box 573, Folder 1)
      - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit (Box 573, Folder 2)
      - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - Brochure (Box 573, Folder 3-4)
      - Pocantico Hills - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 574, Folder 1-3)